fontshop.com 2008-06-21

# Privacy Policy | FontShop

By accessing or using this Website, you agree to the terms of FontShop International’s Online Privacy Policy, as outlined below. If you do not agree to these terms, please do not access or use this site. FontShop International reserves the right to change the Online Privacy Policy from time to time at its sole discretion. Your use of this site will be subject to the most current version of the Online Privacy Policy at the time of such use.

## Collection of personal information

When you engage in certain activities on this site, such as viewing prices, ordering or selecting products, downloading software, or entering contests, FontShop International may ask you to provide certain information about yourself by filling out and submitting an online form. It is completely optional for you to engage in these activities. If you elect to engage in these activities, however, FontShop International may ask that you provide us personal information, such as: your name, address, phone number, e-mail address and if you download products we will require your credit card details.

## How your personal information is used

FontShop International collects your information in order to record and support your participation in the activities you select. If you order a product that is to be electronically downloaded, for example, the information is used to verify credit cards, issue multi-user license documents, re-deliver orders in the case of transmission failure and to maintain your customer history.

## Protection of your personal information

The personal information that you provide is protected in several ways. Access by you to your personal information is available through a password and unique customer ID selected by you. We recommend that you do not divulge your password to anyone. In addition, your personal information resides on a secure server that only selected FontShop International personnel may access via password. FontShop International protects your credit card transaction using SSL encryption and thereby prevents unauthorized parties from viewing such information when it is being transmitted to FontShop International. We do not sell or divulge your personal information to third parties.

## Use of cookies

When you visit www.FontShop.com, you can surf the site anonymously and access most information without revealing your identity. In order to enable our shopping system to work for you, we use ’cookies’ for automated administration purposes. A cookie is small amount of data that is transferred to your browser by a Webserver and can only be read by the server that gave it to you. It functions as your identification card, helping to correlate your passwords, purchases, and preferences to your personal browser. It cannot be executed as code or deliver viruses.

Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the option to decide whether or not to accept it. (For Web pages that require an authorization, cookies are not optional. Users who choose not to accept cookies will not be able to use all functions properly.)

While FontShop International uses cookies to ensure proper functioning of the shopping system, and our Webserver automatically logs the Internet IP address of your computer, this information does not identify you personally and you remain completely anonymous unless you have otherwise provided FontShop International with personal information.

## Updating your personal information

You have the right to access and correct your personal information and privacy preferences at any time. To edit your Registration Information, simply log into your [Account Settings](https://www.fontshop.com/account/account_edit.php). The registration automatically appears, and permits you to view and edit your address details. You may also access and correct your personal information and privacy preferences by writing or calling 1 415 252 1003 at: 

FSI Fonts & Software USA, Inc  
149 9th Street  
San Francisco CA 94103  
USA  
1 415 252 1003  
1 415 252 1331
